University of Connecticut, Vice President for Academic Affairs Office Records [Anthony DiBenedetto and Julius A. Elias, 1981-1988] 1998.0154
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series XVIII: Department of Higher Education, 1979-1989
  - New Hampshire College relicensure, 1983 (Box 46:, Folder 1443)
  - Off-campus offerings, 1983-1989 (Box 46:, Folder 1444-1446)
  - Office of Policy and Management (OPM), 1982-1987 (Box 46:, Folder 1447)
  - OPM Budget hearing, 1986-1987 (Box 46:, Folder 1448)
  - Proposed constituent unit mission statement, 1986 (Box 46:, Folder 1449)
  - Staff recommendation: Budget, 1989 (Box 46:, Folder 1450)
  - Statewide Data Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 46:, Folder 1451)
  - Strategic Plan Steering Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 46:, Folder 1452-1453)
  - Strategic Task Force, 1987 (Box 46:, Folder 1454)
  - Student Assessment Program, 1987 (Box 46:, Folder 1455)
  - Tuition Policy Proposal, 1983-1984 (Box 46:, Folder 1456)
- Series XIX: Non-University Organizations and Outside Agencies, undated, 1978-1989
  - Aetna Companies, 1983-1988 (Box 47:, Folder 1457-1459)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1984-1989 (Box 47:, Folder 1460-1462)
  - American Can Company, 1984-1985 (Box 47:, Folder 1463)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1983 (Box 47:, Folder 1464)
  - American Council on Education, 1984-1989 (Box 47:, Folder 1465-1466)
  - American Telephone and Telegraph, 1984-1986 (Box 47:, Folder 1467-1469)
  - Artic Research Consortium, 1988 (Box 47:, Folder 1470)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1989 (Box 47:, Folder 1471)
  - Burger King, 1987 (Box 47:, Folder 1472)
  - Central Connecticut State University, 1989 (Box 47:, Folder 1473)
  - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1984 (Box 47:, Folder 1474)
  - Chongqing University, 1989 (Box 47:, Folder 1475)
  - Colonial Bancorp, 1983 (Box 47:, Folder 1476)
  - Combined Health Appeal, 1983 (Box 47:, Folder 1477)
  - Computing Sciences Accreditation Board, Inc., 1986 (Box 47:, Folder 1478)
  - Connecticut Academy of Science and Engineering, 1983-1985 (Box 47:, Folder 1479-1480)
  - Connecticut Association for Continuing Education/Aetna, 1982 (Box 47:, Folder 1481)
  - Connecticut Association of Latin-Americans in Higher Education, 1989 (Box 47:, Folder 1482)
  - Connecticut Business and Industry Association, 1981-1982 (Box 47:, Folder 1483)
  - Connecticut Evaluation and Training Center Corporation, 1982 (Box 47:, Folder 1484)
  - Connecticut State Technical Colleges, 1989 (Box 47:, Folder 1485)
  - Control Data, 1984-1986 (Box 47:, Folder 1486)
  - Council for Chemical Research, 1981-1984 (Box 47:, Folder 1487-1488)
  - Council of Presidents/Academic Affairs, 1982-1989 (Box 47:, Folder 1489-1495)
  - Data General, 1985 (Box 47:, Folder 1496)
  - Digital, 1984 (Box 47:, Folder 1497)
  - Eastern Connecticut State University, 1989 (Box 47:, Folder 1498)
  - Field Publications, 1986 (Box 47:, Folder 1499)
  - Ford Foundation, 1987 (Box 47:, Folder 1500)
  - General Electric Foundation, 1988 (Box 47:, Folder 1501)
  - Haskins Laboratories, 1989 (Box 47:, Folder 1502)
  - Hispanic Leadership Fellows Program, 1984-1986 (Box 47:, Folder 1503-1504)
  - International Association of Universities, 1989 (Box 48:, Folder 1505)
  - International Business Machines (IBM), 1984-1987 (Box 48:, Folder 1506-1508)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1983 (Box 48:, Folder 1509)
  - Kennedy Foundation, 1983 (Box 48:, Folder 1510)
  - Kresge Foundation, 1985-1989 (Box 48:, Folder 1511)
  - Matsushita Foundation, 1986 (Box 48:, Folder 1512)
  - National Achievement Scholarship Program, 1982 (Box 48:, Folder 1513)
  - National Agencies
    - ACE- AFL-CIO, 1989 (Box 48:, Folder 1514)
    - American Association of University Women, 1989 (Box 48:, Folder 1515)
    - NUCEA, 1989 (Box 48:, Folder 1516)
    - U.S. Department of Education, 1989 (Box 48:, Folder 1517)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1983-1988 (Box 48:, Folder 1518-1525)
  - National Center for Higher Education Management Systems, 1988 (Box 48:, Folder 1526)
  - National Consortium for Education Access, 1987 (Box 48:, Folder 1527)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1984 (Box 48:, Folder 1528)
  - National Science Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 48:, Folder 1529)
  - New England Board of Higher Education, 1982-1989 (Box 48:, Folder 1530-1533)
  - New England Center for Continuing Education, 1983-1987 (Box 48:, Folder 1534)
  - New England Land Grant Universities, 1984-1985 (Box 48:, Folder 1535-1536)
  - Pekin Elmer Corporation, 1980 (Box 48:, Folder 1537)
  - Pfizer, Inc., 1978-1984 (Box 48:, Folder 1538)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1981 (Box 48:, Folder 1539)
  - Plastics Engineers, Society of, 1981 (Box 48:, Folder 1540)
  - Plenum Publishing Corporation, 1983 (Box 48:, Folder 1541)
  - Root-Tilden Scholarship Program, 1981 (Box 48:, Folder 1552)
  - Science and Technology Institute of New England, undated (Box 48:, Folder 1553)
  - Southern New England Telephone, 1986 (Box 48:, Folder 1554)
  - Study of Sport in Society, Center for, 1987-1988 (Box 48:, Folder 1555)
  - State Agencies
    - Department of Economic Development, 1986 (Box 48:, Folder 1556)
    - Office of Policy and Management, 1988-1989 (Box 48:, Folder 1557)
  - Syracuse University, 1989 (Box 48:, Folder 1558)
  - Tropical Studies, Organization for, 1983-1989 (Box 48:, Folder 1559)
  - Union Carbide Corporation, 1983 (Box 48:, Folder 1560)
  - United Technologies Corporation, 1983-1984 (Box 48:, Folder 1561)
  - United Way, 1984-1985 (Box 48:, Folder 1562)
  - UConn Professional Employee Association, 1988-1989 (Box 48:, Folder 1563)
  - University Patents, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 48:, Folder 1564)
  - University Press, 1984 (Box 48:, Folder 1565)
  - Universities Research Association, 1987-1988 (Box 48:, Folder 1566)
  - Water Conservancy, Institute of, 1984 (Box 48:, Folder 1567)
  - Xenogen, 1984 (Box 48:, Folder 1568)
  - Xerox Corporation, 1985-1987 (Box 48:, Folder 1569)
  - Yale Visiting Faculty Program, 1982-1989 (Box 48:, Folder 1570-1577)
    General note
    Return to Provost's Office Records.